Good morning from the dead of night!
Mayonaka Punch!
Live here!
You really went to a desert island.
Two hundred thousand views?!
*NO ESCAPE* 1 Week Desert Island Survival
200k views   1 week ago   ...more
Mayonaka Punch
30k subscribers
Wowie!
That's nothing for me.
Awesome!
What kind of videos are you all watching?
This one for me.
We're doing this for music class.
We're practicing as a group.
Teamwork is key.
We need to all be in sync.
Yu-kun!
Mama!
I should be heading home, too.
Me, too!
Later!
Eh?
So it's here...
Wait, it's just an old office building.
Is this really the place?
A-Are you okay?
Y-Yeah.
Let's go.
Caution
Watch Your Fingers
Ichiko's Wish
At around seven o'clock this evening,
Sudden House Collapse Remains Mystery
there was an explosion of unknown
origin in this quiet neighborhood.
Nearby Residents Concerned
Lives in Vicinity
Man, it just suddenly collapsed
and scared me to death.
The cause? Beats me.
Maybe a gigantic bat or something?
Or maybe a goddess came bursting out!
Sudden House Collapse Remains Mystery
As you can see, local residents
continue to offer cryptic comments...
Do you know why you were
summoned here to home base?
Um...
About what happened at Banpai Manor...
We're terribly sorry!
So Mother's behind that curtain?
I can't make her out at all.
We've allowed you to make videos.
But I believe we said
not to cause any commotion.
Yes.
So how did this come about?
Well, um...
Girls!
Enjoying the drinks I bought
with my gambling winnings?
Yeah!
Toss me up in the air!
And a one! And a two!
And a three!
We're so very sorry!
Sorry!
Banpai Manor will be demolished.
What?!
D-Demolished?
On Mother's orders.
You wrecked Banpai Manor,
attracted the public's attention,
and risked humans discovering
the existence of vampires.
It's only natural that
you'd be punished for it.
You're a bunch of bad oranges!
Or so Mother says.
What's she mean by bad oranges?
Is that a proverb?
Um, there's an old TV drama...
You there!
Cut the chatter!
So sorry!
If you tear down Banpai Manor, where do we go?!
You'll be moved to a different house
where we keep troublemakers.
Hey!
What about me, then?!
Don't care. Do what you want.
It's hard to shoot videos
unless we live together!
What happens to your videos
is none of my concern.
You can't!
Masaki needs to be with me!
For my sake!
I'd be scared living with
vampires I don't know!
I'm also opposed to moving out.
The local pachinko parlor is the only one
that has Ichijo-kun to tune the pins for me!
I don't want that, either!
I really don't want to lose Banpai Manor!
You have no room to complain
after all the trouble you've caused!
I haven't caused any trouble here!
And who was the one
who racked up all that debt?
It's not our fault the wall got wrecked!
The alcohol's to blame!
After all that's happened,
you're really blaming the bottle?
They say, "Condemn the crime,
not the criminal!"
I apologize for what I said!
It was all my fault!
Yes!
Here.
Man, that hurt.
Don't go causing any more headaches for Mother!
Live-sama.
Let's go ask them again
not to demolish our home!
Still, you know, they said
we could keep shooting videos.
Maybe moving isn't such a bad idea.
Or, heck, maybe it's a great one!
Weren't you against it before?
What's this?
Things to Check Before Living Together!
What's the best room layout for two people?
What to consider
when renting to share
"The best room layout for two people"?!
You're going to live with Masaki?!
No, that's not it!
You've got it all wrong!
I'm going to have Masaki
teach me how to edit videos.
And to do that, I'll need to spend time
over at her place, right?
So we might gradually end up
living together, you know!
In other words, as long as
you can be alone with Masaki,
you don't need Banpai Manor anymore?
No, that's not what I mean.
I-I don't think it's happening.
You too, Fu?!
We can't go against Mother's decision.
I'm fine wherever I end up going.
So long as I can gamble.
What do you mean?
I came to a realization.
No matter where I end up moving,
I can just fly on over here.
You're the one who wrecked the wall.
I-I'm not the only one to blame here!
That's right!
Everyone else except me is at fault!
But I'm the only one taking the
future of Banpai Manor seriously!
What a pain.
Did you just call me a pain?!
You're the only one who cares
so much about Banpai Manor here!
Tokage!
You can't tell her the truth like that!
Please say it a little nicer!
I mean, let's be honest. It's a bother.
You all agree with me, don't you?
Is that right?!
I get it! I'm nothing but a bother!
So be it, then!
I'll take care of everything all by myself!
I-Ichiko, calm down.
I'm perfectly calm! Cool as a cucumber!
Well, I'm leaving, since I'm out of balls.
Ah!
I-I need to go to work!
I can't believe it slipped my mind!
Sorry. I don't know how to play pachinko.
Children shouldn't be playing pachinko.
How old are you, young lady?
A hundred and ten.
They just don't understand
how precious Banpai Manor is.
Well, they'll come back crying in no time.
I won't hold it against them when they do.
Since I'm a good girl.
If we all eat a meal together
with everyone's favorite food in it,
I'm sure they'll all see the light!
One question.
Yes?
Vampires can subsist on blood alone,
so why do you eat food?
That's because I suggested it.
Eating meals together, that is.
Why's that?
I was originally a human,
so before I came here, I'd eat dinner
with my mom, my dad, and my brothers.
So if a vampire drinks my blood,
will I turn into one, too?
That's not an issue.
Besides, I drank your blood already, didn't I?
Oh, that's right.
It's actually the reverse.
Humans turn into vampires when
vampire blood enters their body.
Then why'd you become a vampire?
I can't answer that.
What?
I'd love to have stayed a human,
living with the rest of my family.
But I was turned into a vampire
with no warning.
Mother keeps them in check nowadays,
but in the past, vampires went around turning
humans into vampires against their will.
And so, I lost my humanity,
with nowhere to return and nowhere to go.
Spending all my time alone,
walking and walking.
It was then that I stumbled
upon Banpai Manor...
and Live-sama welcomed me in.
I knew I could survive without eating food,
but I wanted to eat with everyone,
so I always cooked for us.
Day after day,
after day,
after day...
until Live-sama sat at the table.
And Tokage as well,
followed by Fu.
Ever since, we've always eaten
together at Banpai Manor.
That's why Banpai Manor
is the home that I love.
That story was heavier than I thought,
and now my chest hurts.
Is that so?
Also, why hot pot in the summer?
Because we can put everyone's
favorite foods in it!
I'm starving!
Not yet!
What?
Let's eat, let's eat, let's eat!
We'll eat when everyone's here.
Got it.
What're you doing?
L-Live-sama!
Don't sneak up on me like that!
Let me take a quick peek inside...
Why hot pot on a hot day like this?
Dunno.
So this is where you were.
Hey!
Masaki-san!
What's with the get-up?!
I'm going to talk it out in person with Mother.
What?!
Since none of you are any use.
Wait, wait!
You're gonna go in there armed like that?
You're totally ready to fight!
Shut up!
I don't care what someone who
can't stick up for a friend has to say!
I'm real hungry here!
This house is important to her, isn't it?
You should be the first ones
to sympathize with her!
We can finally eat.
Ichiko, time for some grub!
Make sure there's liver in there.
Um, crown daisy leaves too, if you will.
Oh, you've got enoki mushrooms as well!
Live, save some for the rest of us!
You're recording this?
Hot pot in summer might
make for a funny video.
Meals really are best eaten
with everyone... right?
Live-sama...
Everyone...
All right.
Time to eat—
What's with your manners?!
Why did you come in through the wall?!
We have a front door!
Also, you need to wash
your hands before you eat!
Huh? You're really getting angry now?
Okay, let's start the
Don't Demolish Banpai Manor Project.
What exactly does that involve?
Are we storming the place with garlic?
If we do that, we'll be erased.
To be honest, pleading with her
will get us nowhere.
Maybe we'd have more of a chance if
we showed her how much we've grown.
Grown? I'm growing every day.
Huh?
We're doing this for music class.
We're practicing as a group.
Teamwork is key.
We need to all be in sync.
I have an idea!
Bam!
Take a look!
If we can pull this off, I'm sure
Mother will change her mind!
Seriously?
Karate Dojo
You'll be in for it if you waste
Mother's time on something stupid.
I swear...
Join a Meeting
Sign Up
Sign In
N-Now's my chance to see Mother's face.
Join with Computer Audio
Test Speaker and Microphone
Mother
O-Or not.
So? What do you want?
Mother
In our time living at Banpai Manor,
we've slowly learned to cooperate,
and we continue to grow!
Mother
We're not bad oranges!
And we're about to prove it!
Yes!
And in the case that we do,
we ask you to cancel
the demolition of Banpai Manor!
Please!
Mother
As you can see, our hearts
are perfectly joined as one.
As such, continuing to live together
should pose no problem. Wouldn't you agree?
I see.
You did well.
Like hell I'd say that!
Who do you take me for?!
That wasn't enough to melt your heart?!
For real?!
I apologize, Mother.
It ended up being a waste of your time.
Banpai Manor will, as planned—
Please don't!
Hey!
Don't demolish Banpai Manor!
After all that, you still won't give up?!
I don't wanna!
No! No!
Don't be so childish! You're being a bother!
Ichiko...
After I stopped being human,
I was alone all the time.
But they ate dinner with me like I asked.
They all did,
even though they don't need to eat.
It was my own childish demand,
but they've put up with it all this time.
So I've always been a bother.
Live-sama. Tokage. Fu.
I'm sorry.
Mother
Look at this video!
What now?
Just watch!
Masaki!
How long are you going to keep recording?
A little longer.
I swear.
You really love making us
work our socks off, huh?
That meat is mine!
They may all be pieces of garbage,
worse than rotten orange peels...
She never went that far!
Mother
They only care about themselves, never
agree on anything, and are totally useless...
But here they are,
sitting down for dinner together.
Not because they were forced to.
They're acting out of compassion for Ichiko!
Because...
they're the kind of people who
can think about others, too!
Mother
You—
You can't be the only ones
who get special treatment!
What do you mean by that?
You—
If we turned a blind eye to
all the trouble you've caused
it would set a bad example
for the rest of the vampires!
We're not troublemakers anymore!
Then just what are you?
We're MayoPan!
Huh?
That's right!
We're doing our best to make videos!
Yeah, yeah!
So what if—
And they're all growing as time goes on!
Yeah, yeah!
So what—
A-At first, I thought, "Why videos? Why me?"
But now I enjoy it!
Like I said, so what—
Yeah, yeah!
Shut your trap!
Sure, we've still got a long way to go.
Still...
One day, we'll become NewTubers
with over a million subs!
We'll become so big,
there'll be no room for complaints!
So let us live together, here in Banpai Manor.
Pretty please!
Please!
Mother
Six months.
What?
Mother
A million subscribers in six months.
Reach that number,
and I'll call off the demolition.
Mother
What?!
H-Hold it!
Six months is impossible!
Give us a year, at least!
Mother
End Meeting
We only have a little over
twenty thousand right now... so...
Mother has left the meeting.
She hung up.
A million subs in six months.
To be honest, that'll be tough.
But!
Mayonaka Punch has no choice but to do it!
For Masaki's blood and for Banpai Manor!
Yes!
You're right!
Yeah!
Okay, all together now!
Time to eat!
Ichiko
Sent you a sticker
Goodnight
We're Breaking Up
How do we get a million subs?!
Let's just borrow some money
and give it all away!
Ichiko.
Y-Yuki-sama!
More debts?
I-I'm just kidding!
K-Kidding... Agh!
Next time: "Your Faves Are Adorbs,
Hit That Subscribe"!
Your Faves Are Adorbs, Hit That Subscribe
Make sure you support me as well.